Komaichu: It's good that you're eating beans.
こまいちゅう 豆食べてるのがいいよ
picture?
え?
Are you eating beans?
豆食べてる?
The beans here are still in there.
ここの豆まだ入ってるよ
With stones.
石付きだして
Get me a stone.
石付きだしてよ
You did your best.
頑張ったね
I don't try hard.
頑張らない
It's warm when I stop.
私が止まったら温かい
結構
But if I made it stronger, it wouldn't have to be empty.
だってでも強くしたら空いちゃいけなくて
Wait, wait, wait.
待って、待って、待って
Ai-chan, Ai-chan, it's here.
あいちゃん、あいちゃん、ここだ
Here's what you should have.
持つべきはここです
I have to go this way.
私 はこっちを行っちゃうといかないと
Well, this is it.
そりゃあ、こっちだもん
You did your best.
頑張ったね
I'm tired.
疲れてる
Here, here, here.
こ っち、こっち、こっち
picture?
え?
You want to see the night view, right?
夜景見たいでしょ?
In this outfit?
この格好で?
You want to see the night view, right?
夜景見たいでしょ、だって
Yeah, but I thought we'd watch it together later.
そうだけど、後で二人で見ようと思ったのに
You can see Tokyo Tower.
東京タワーとか見えるよ
I can't see Tokyo Tower.
東京タワーは見えないよ
appear?
見える?
where?
どこ?
There are no days when I look at the night view.
夜景見てる日もないじゃん
Can I see it?
見ていいの?
Is the scenery beautiful?
景色きれい?
I haven't seen it!
見てない!
Oh, wait, yellowtail.
あ、待って、ぶり
Beautiful feet too.
足もきれい
Your feet are beautiful too.
足もきれいじゃん
I'm falling!
落ちちゃう!
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
drop down?
落ちる?
Good.
よいしょ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
What are you doing?
何してんの?
Hey, hey, hey.
ねえ、ねえ、ねえ
I'm going to fall.
落ちちゃうって
Good.
よいしょ
Why don't you just ride?
そのまま乗ってごらん?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Get on your waist.
腰につく
Can't you come near me?
近くに入んない?
I'm hiding something.
なんか隠すの
Huh?
あれ?
Can you turn around?
後ろ向いてごらん?
behind?
後ろ?
I let a lot of it out.
中にいっぱい出しちゃったんだけど
Did it come out?
出たか?
Please wait a moment and check.
ちょっと待って確認してみて
eye
め
I fell asleep today.
っちゃ 寝ちゃった、今日
Because it's been a while.
久々だったから
how was it?
どうだった?
I'm tired.
疲れちゃったね
cute.
かわいい
I've made a reservation at a restaurant today.
今日はレストラン予約してるからさ
Let's take a little break and then go.
ちょっと ゆっくり休憩してから行こうね
Are you hungry?
お腹すいたでしょ?
Take a break.
ちょっと休憩して
I might try it again.
もう一回しちゃうかもしれない
There are no erotic records left.
エログ残ってないよ
What are you doing?
何してんの?
I was watching the video.
動画見てた
movie?
動画?
Yeah, YouTube.
うん、YouTube
What?
なあに?
how was it?
どうだった?
restaurant.
レストラン
It was delicious, amazing.
おいしかったよ、すごい
I totally understand.
めっちゃわかったね
It was delicious.
おいしかった
This kind of place is delicious.
こういうところのおいしい
After all, this kind of place is delicious.
こういうところのおいしいやっぱり
What was delicious?
何がおいしかった?
number one.
一番
What is it?
なんだろう?
Is it roast beef?
やっぱローストビーフかな?
Roast beef, that's it.
ローストビーフね、あれね
It had some weird seasonings in it.
変な調味料入ってたね
what?
何?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
I'm not used to things that are that expensive.
あんまり高いやつが慣れてないからさ
It tastes weird.
変な味だ
Oh, really?
え、そう?
what?
なに?
Are you going to sleep yet?
もう寝る?
What?
なあに?
I thought it was kind of cute.
なんかかわいいなと思って
Is it a kamacho?
かまちょなんですか?
Kamacho?
かまちょ?
What's the kamacho?
かまちょなに?
I thought it was cute.
かわいいなと思って
thank you.
ありがとう
It's huge.
めっちゃでかいよ
Look.
ほら
That's disgusting.
むかむかだね
What?
なあに?
This is a little big, isn't it?
ちょっとおっきいでしょ、これ
It's tough, isn't it?
きついでしょ
It's cold if I don't wear this.
これ着てないと寒いから
I want to warm you up.
俺が温めたいよ
Are you going to warm it up?
温めてくるの?
fault.
あら
Look, it's cold.
ほら寒いじゃん
cold?
寒い?
You did it earlier, right?
さっきしたでしょ
You won't turn it on when you sleep, right?
寝るときつけないでしょ、これだって
I can't wear it though.
着けないけどさ
You can't wear it.
着 けないでしょ
Well, you can't wear it at home.
おうちではまぁ着けないでしょ
What?
なあに?
It's ticklish though.
くすぐったいんだけど
What is it?
なんですか?
Why is this happening?
なんでこんなことになってるの?
What?
な あに?
Maybe it's because I got some nutrition.
ちょっと栄養取ったからかもしれない
picture?
え?
There's nothing like that in that dish.
あの料理にそんなものは入っていません
lie?
うそ?
It's not in there.
入 ってないよ
Wasn't it in?
入ってなかった?
Like a soft-shelled turtle?
すっぽみたいな?
There isn't.
ないよ
I don't think so.
多 分ないと思うよ
Where is this?
ここは?
a little bit.
ちょっと
What are you doing?
何してんの?
One body.
一体
What are you doing?
何してんの?
What do you want to do?
何をしたいの?
What?
何って?
It's like this.
せっかくこんなさ
Because I got some nutrition.
栄養取ったから
Because I got nutrients.
栄 養 取ったから
Will you?
するの?
yes.
そう
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
You shouldn't take it seriously like that.
そんなまじまじと見るもんじゃないでしょ
Shall we do it?
しちゃう?
want?
欲しい?
want.
欲しい
Then just say you want it.
じゃあ欲しいって言ってほら
What do you want?
何が欲しい?
Wait here.
待ってほら
You want a dick, right?
ちんちん欲しいでしょ?
I want a penis.
ちんちん欲しい
amazing.
すごい
Don't you have to put in any effort?
力入んない?
what up?
どうした?
Because it feels good.
気持ちいいから
It's really closed.
すっごい閉まってるね
Wipe it quickly.
早く拭いて
Looks like it'll fit in.
入りそう
I couldn't even fight.
喧嘩もできなかった
Wipe it before that.
その前に拭いて
I can't open my eyes.
目が開かないよ
Do you want to sleep like this?
この まま寝る?
I won't sleep like this.
このまま寝ない
Because it gets in your eyes.
目に入っちゃうから